thedesignmag.com 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy

**We are dedicated to defending your privacy**  
We collect the minimum quantity of information about you that is corresponding to providing you with a satisfactory assistance. This Plan indicates the kind of processes that may result in information being gathered about you. The purpose of this is to enable you to understand which individual determining information (“PII”, “Personal Information”) of yours is gathered, how and when we might use your information, who has entry to this information, and how you can appropriate any discrepancies in information.

**Information Collected**  
We may collect any or all of information that via both automated means such as devices information. Personal Information you give us depends on the kind of assistance or sale inquiry and may include your name, deal with, variety, fax variety and current e-mail deal with, dates of assistance offered, types of assistance offered, transaction history, manner of transaction, quantity of expenses, date of expenses, sector deal with, bank cards or other transaction information. The economical information will be moved only be used to bill you for the service and solutions you purchased. If you purchase by bank cards, this information may be sent to your bank cards provider. All sensitive information is gathered on a protected server and information is moved. When shifting individual information a security symbol will appear in your internet browser.

**Information Use**  
This information is used for expenses and to offer assistance and assistance to our clients. We may also study this information to determine our clients’ needs and offer assistance for our clients. All affordable safety measures are taken to avoid unexpected entry to this information. This protect may need you to offer extra forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your consideration information. Thedesignmag.com may e-mail its monthly news letter to the primary get in touch with e-mail on file, but clients are able to opt out of this news letter whenever they want.

**Log Files**  
We use IP information to evaluate trends, provide our website and hosts, track accessibility, and collect wide market information for combination use. IP information are not linked to your individual information. It is possible that individual information about a client may be involved in the log data files due to the normal functions of IP information and Web browsing.

**Cookies**  
Your Web internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text data files – “cookies” – that hold information which allows a web page to recognize your consideration. We use biscuits to save your choices and sign in information, and offer customized performance. You can decline biscuits by changing your internet browser settings, but be aware that this will turn off some of the performance on the Thedesignmag.com’s web page. More information about biscuits can be found at http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie.

**Disclosing Information**  
We do not reveal any individual information obtained about you from this web page to third events. This does not implement to associates that offer solutions to you depending on links offered within your CPanel accessibility and management, wherein information will be shared to assist in your use of extra services involved with your web host account  
We may use individual information to keep in touch with you and inform you of improvements associated with our business. We may also reveal combination, unknown information depending on information gathered from customers to potential partners, our associates, and reputable third events. We take all available actions to select associates and companies that are moral and offer similar privacy security to their clients and the community. We do not create any representations about the methods and policies about these companies.

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**  
If a client’s your individual information changes, or if a client no longer desires our solutions, we will endeavor to offer a way to appropriate, upgrade or eliminate that client’s individual information in our records. Otherwise, please get in touch with us at Anshu.shukla@thedesignmag.com  
Opt Out & Modifications  
By standard, clients do receive any non-reflex program up-dates, such as the updates, accounts, and messages. Any client who willingly gets these up-dates may remove yourself from list whenever they want. Customers may not opt out of possibly receiving important program announcements, in the rare event that such alert would be necessary.  
Security

Thedesignmag.com’s uses technical measures to avoid the loss, neglect, alternation or unwanted disclosure of information under our management. Thedesignmag.com’s uses measures such as and not limited to: physical, electronic and managing procedures to protect and protected information we collect on the internet. When we ask clients or customers to offer economical information (such as a bank cards number) that information is protected using Secure Electrical sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**  
We work with govt and government bodies to implement and conform to the law. We will reveal any information about Users upon valid request by govt or law government bodies as we, in our sole attention, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without restriction subpoenas), to protected your residence and privileges, or the residence and privileges of a third party, to protected the safety of the public or anyone, or stop activity we consider illegal or illegal.

**Changes to this Policy**  
Any changes to our policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our policy. We will take affordable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Plan. However, to be prepared, we suggest that you read this paper everytime you use the web page to ensure that it still meets with your approval.  
Enforcement and Argument Resolution

Thedesignmag.com’s has established internal systems to confirm its ongoing sticking with its privacy policy. Thedesignmag.com also motivates individuals covered by this privacy policy to raise any issues about our handling of individual information by getting in touch with Thedesignmag.com.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about our policy, or if you want to know what information we have gathered about you, please e-mail us at Anshu.shukla@thedesignmag.com. You can also appropriate any actual mistakes in that information or need us to eliminate your information from any list under our management. You can also e-mail us at Anshu.shukla@thedesignmag.com..
